<SampleDefinition
    name      = "CEGUISample_CustomShapesDrawing"
    type      = "C++ Module"
    summary         = "This sample displays rendering possibilities provided with CEGUI's GeometryBuffer and SVGImage/SVGData class.
    The goal is to render an FPS graph that displays the last recorded FPS values. SVGImage provides optional anti-aliasing and the possibility to
    use the Image as part of a window"
    description     = "In CEGUI the GeometryBuffer can be used to render vertices directly on the screen. However, this comes with limitations,
                       since CEGUI is not a Rendering Engine. For example only textured and coloured vertices are available out of the box. The vertices for all lines and
                       the quad of the background of the graph had to be calculated with extra code. The other possibility to render a graph, as display in this sample, 
                       is by using an SVGImage. Each SVGImage points to a (possibly shared) SVGData object that contains its data. This data can be modified by adding shapes based
                       on the SVG BasicShapes. The vertices do not have to be calculated in this case and the rendering specifics like colours and line widths can be specified
                       more conveniently. Additionally, with SVGImages it is possible to switch on anti-aliasing, which is implemented by adding additional blending geometry to all shapes. 
                       Also, it is easily possible to add the SVGImage to a window, by referring to it via a property, which is not possible with the GeometryBuffer method. This is
                       displayed in the sample with a WindowsLook/FrameWindow that contains an Generic/Image window. The FrameWindow is sizeable and will also scale its child window when
                       sized. The Generic/Image window has an 'Image' property that is pointing to our SVGImage. When the FrameWindow is sized it can thus be seen that the image is 
                       being scaled too."
    credits         = "Lukas &quot;Ident&quot; Meindl"
/>
